Contact

p-mason@live.com

www.linkedin.com/in/phyllis-mason-a6801a14 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Case Managment Social Services Medical Education

Phyllis Mason

RN Clinical Manager

Greater San Diego Area

Summary

Experienced Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the mental health care industry. Skilled in Nonprofit Organizations, Crisis Intervention, Clinical Supervision, Dual Diagnosis, and Physician Relations. Strong healthcare services professional graduated from University of Mobile.

Experience

North County Health Services (NCHS) RN Clinical Mgr. II October 2018 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Tri-City Medical Center Registered Nurse May 2017 - Present (3 years 3 months) Oceanside, California

Aya Healthcare
Psych Nurse (Traveler)
January 2017 - Present (3 years 7 months)
USA

Nursing Referral Svc Travel Registered Nurse August 2016 - Present (4 years) Working as a psych RN in different healthcare facilities.

AHS - BayView-COP-Trans Age Services Nurse Manager 2000 - 2016 (16 years)

Education

University of Mobile
Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2003)

University of Mobile
Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2003)